Guide to the Harper & Row, Publishers Records,
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series IV: Business Files
  - Misc. Papers and Reports
  - Hamish Hamilton Pension Scheme, [n.p.], 1948
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Preference and Ordinary Stock, etc.
  - Hamish Hamilton Law Books, Ltd Reports, [n.p.], 1944 and prior years
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Records of Dividends Received
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Salary Lists, etc.
  - Hamilton, Hamish, [n.p.], 1949-1953 (Box 200)
  - Hamilton, Hamish, [n.p.], 1954-1960
  - Correspondence Re Hamish Hamilton Ltd.
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1931 - June 30 1932
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1932 - June 30 1933
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1933 - June 30, 1934
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1934 - June 30, 1935
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1935 - June 30, 1936
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1936 - June 30, 1937
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1937 - June 30, 1938
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Year, [n.p.], July 1, 1938 - June 30, 1939
  - Harper & Row Report, [n.p.], 1928
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd, Misc. Papers, [n.p.], Jan-Feb 1946
  - Hamish Hamilton Law Books Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1945-1946 (Box 201)
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1946
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1945
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1944
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1943
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1942
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1941
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1940
  - Hamish Hamilton Misc.
  - Hamish Hamilton Reports, [n.p.], 1954
  - Hamish Hamilton Reports, [n.p.], 1953
  - Hamish Hamilton Reports, [n.p.], 1952
  - Hamish Hamilton Reports, [n.p.], 1951
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd Papers re. Capital Stock & Financial Papers (Box 202)
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd, [n.p.], July-Dec. 1939
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1950
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1949
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1948
  - Hamish Hamilton Ltd. Reports, [n.p.], 1947
  - Hamilton, Hamish, [n.p.], 1966
  - Hamilton, Hamish, [n.p.], 1961-1965
  - He - Hz (Box 203)
  - Hanna, Mark
  - Harper Atlantic Advertising
  - Harper & Row Ltd.
  - Harper & Brothers public
  - Harper and Row, [n.p.], 1962-1964
  - Harper & Row, [n.p.], 1965 - 1966 (Box 204)
  - Harper & Row, [n.p.], 1967 - 1968
  - Harper & Row, [n.p.], 1969 - 1971
  - Harper Art Library
  - Harpercrest
  - Harpers Magazine press
  - Harpers Magazine, [n.p.], 1966-1968
  - Harpers Magazine, [n.p.], 1969-1970
  - Harpers Magazine, [n.p.], 71 - (Box 205)
  - Harper's Magazine Projections and operating statements, [n.p.], 6/65 - 12/66
  - Harper's Magazine Statements, [n.p.], 1967
  - Harper's Magazine Financial Statements, [n.p.], 1968 (Box 206)
  - Statements, [n.p.], 1969 - 1970
  - Statements, [n.p.], 1971
  - Harpers Magazine Press
  - Harper Reprint Series
  - Harrison, George L. (Box 207)
  - Hartman, Lee Foster
  - Harwood, Raymond
  - Hospitalized veterans writing project
  - India, Japan - Mysore
  - Interdepartmental royalty agreements
  - International, [n.p.], 1974-1975
  - International (Box 208)
  - Inventory
  - J 10 (Box 209)
  - J & J Harper Editions
  - J & J Harper
  - Jobbers
  - Jones, Gordon (Box 210)
  - Junior
  - Juvenile
  - Knopf, Alfred
  - Kodansha
  - L 12 (Box 211)
  - Large type editions
  - Lawrence, Elizabeth
  - Leased cars
    [Trans to M. Myerson 11/69]
  - Legal
  - Library (Box 212)
  - Library Club of America
  - Library of Congress Notes
  - Living History - re: Harpers Weekly
  - Lobby - Correspondence with Gilbert
  - , London, 1960
  - , London, 1962
  - , London, 1964
  - , London, 1966
  - M 14 (Box 213)
  - Mc 13
  - Macalester college
  - MacGregor, Frank
  - Macmillan company
  - Macy re: suit under feld
  - Mail order
  - Management Information Survey
  - Manchester
  - Marketing Committee
  - Marketing: corporate task force
  - Marketing Surveys and Research (Box 214)
  - Medical
  - Memos, [n.p.], 8/67 - 12/70
  - Memos, [n.p.], 1/71 - 10/72
  - Memos, [n.p.], 12/74 - 12/75
  - Memos, [n.p.], 11/72 - 1/76
  - Memos: codes (Box 215)
  - Memos: College Department
  - Memos: Computer Analysis/ Reports (Box 216)
  - Memos: Services
  - Microfiche - college department
  - Microform Printing
  - Microfilm
    [See NCR (current)]
  - Monthly Territory Sales Recap. [n.p.], 1971, 1972 (Box 217)
  - Merger
  - N 15
  - NACS-(incl. Meetings and Conventions)
  - National Cash Register
    [See DRM)]
  - National Conference of Christians & Jews
  - New building (Box 218)
  - New York Herald Tribune
  - New York Times
  - Newman, James R. 2nd Science
  - O 16 (Box 219)
  - Office Memos: [n.p.], 1937 - 1958
  - Office Memoranda, [n.p.], 1965-1966
  - Office Memoramda: Bible Reports
  - Office: [n.p.], 1967
  - Office of War Information
  - Old paper book and reprint, [n.p.], 1952-1953 (Box 220)
  - Operations advisory committee
  - Operations reports
  - Out of print
  - P 17 (Box 221)
  - P.E.N.
  - P.I.E. group, [n.p.], 1946-1954
  - P.I.E. group, [n.p.], 1955-1961
  - Pacific books (Box 222)
  - Paperback
  - Paperback
  - Paperback income summaries, [n.p.], 1965-1966
  - Pearn, Pollinger & Higham, Ltd, London, England
  - Pearn, Pollinger & Higham Ltd. English, [n.p.], 1953 - Jan. 1954
  - Penguine
  - Perennial (Box 223)
  - Permissions
  - Peter Smith, publisher
  - Postal
  - Profit and loss
  - Publication Sheets (old)
  - Publication sheets-books not yet published (Box 224)
  - Publications lists
  - Publishers lunch club
  - Publishers' weekly
  - Random House
  - Reader's Digest
  - Religious
  - Reminders
  - Reprint-Memo re policy
  - R 19 (Box 225)
  - Rcords recordings films theater
  - Reminder sale
  - Reprints ordered
  - Returns
  - Returns backlog to '74
  - Rights and Permissions (Box 226)
  - Rights (foreign)
  - Roosevelt, Eleaner
  - Ross & Company
  - Row, Peterson
  - Royalty
  - Russell & Volkening
  - S 20 (Box 227)
  - "S" to 1964 - Authors file
  - S & W - General
  - S & W - Scranton
  - Sales interdepartmental (Box 228)
  - Sales and Salesmen
  - Sales projections
  - Saxon Martha
  - Saxton, E. F. fellowship
  - School department, [n.p.], 1967-1968
  - School department, [n.p.], 1969-1971 (Box 229)
  - Shareholders meeting
  - Society of American Historians
  - Stenographer's notebook, [n.p.], 2/10/76
  - Stenographer's notebook, [n.p.], 3/29/76
  - Strikes, [n.p.], 1941 & 1946
  - Subscriptions & memberships - Subsidiary income
  - (Box 230)
  - T 21
  - Thomas, Evan
  - Tickler file
  - Title control
  - Title screening papers
  - Torchbooks
  - Trade department
  - (Box 231)
  - Trade
  - U 22
  - U.S. Committee for the Atlantic
  - Unions
  - V 23
  - (Box 232)
  - W 24
  - Washington, [n.p.], Jan. 19-21, 1968
  - Weidenfeld & Nicolson, [n.p.], 1955-
  - Weidenfeld & Nicolson, [n.p.], 1953-1954
  - White House library, [n.p.], 1963
  - Write offs
  - X'mas list
  - XYZ 25
- Series V: Financial
  - Subseries V.1: Profit Sharing & Stocks
    - Various financial and stock information (Box Boxes 233 - 243)
- Series VI: Copyright Renewals, Contracts and Rights Reversions
  - Abel, Elie (Box 244)
  - Acton, Harold
  - Agee, James
  - Asimov, Issaac
  - Astor, Brooke
  - Atwood, Margaret
  - Banning, Margaret Culkin
  - Barth, Karl
  - Bawden, Nina
  - Bawden, Nina (Box 245)
  - Bax, Roger
  - Bell, Mary Hayley
  - Belloc, Hilaire
  - Bemelmans, Ludwig
  - Bickel, Alexander M.
  - Blake, Nicholas
  - Borland, Hal G.
  - Borland, Hal (Box 246)
  - Bouton, Jim
  - Bowles, Chester
  - Brown, margaret Wise
  - Buber, Martin
  - Buber, Martin (Box 247)
  - Buchwald, Arthur
  - Buck, Pearl S.
  - Burns, James MacGregor
  - Caldwell, Erskine
  - Canfield, Cass
  - Carr, John Dickson
  - Carr, John Dickson (Box 248)
  - Cary, Joyce
  - Cheever, John
  - Chapin, Harry
  - Ciardi, John (Box 249)
  - Clark, Eugenie
  - Clarke, Authur C.
  - Collier, John
  - Cousteau, Jacques Yves
  - Coward, Noel
  - Creasey, John
  - Creasey, John (Box 250)
  - Crofts, Freeman Wills
  - Cullen, Countee
  - DeHartog, Jan
  - DelaField, E. M.
  - Dogle, A. Conan (Box 251)
  - Dreiser, Theodore
  - Dubois, W. E. B. (Box 252)
  - Drucker, Peter F.
  - Duncan, David Douglas
  - Dworkin, Andrea
  - Elliot, Summer Locke
  - Ellison, Harlan
  - Fitzhugh, Louise
  - Freeling, Nicolas
  - Geva, Tamara
  - Garcia Marquez, Gabriel
  - Garraty, John A.
  - Garve, Andrew
  - Garve, Andrew (Box 253)
  - Gary, Romain
  - George, Jean Craighead
  - Gilbert, Harriet (Box 254)
  - Gilbert, Michael
  - Gunther, John
  - Hammett, Dashiell
  - Harriman, Averell
  - Haycraft, Molly Costain
  - Hecht, Ben & Hayes, Helen
  - Hill, Grace Livingston (Box 255)
  - Hill, Grace Livingston (Box 256)
  - Hill, Grace Livingston (Box 257)
  - Hill, Grace Livingston (Box 258)
  - Hill, Grace Livingston (Box 259)
  - Horgan, Paul
  - Hortler, Sydney
  - Hosken, Clifford
  - Houdin, Harry
  - Hughes, Langston
  - Hunter, Mollie
  - Hurst, Fannie (Box 260)
  - Huxley, Elspeth
  - Huxley, Julian S.
  - Ives, Burl
  - Jameson, Storm
  - Jhabvala, R. Prawer (Box 261)
  - Joad, C. E. M.
  - Jovanovich, William
  - Kaminsky, Max & Hughes, V. E.
  - Kerensky, Alexander
  - Lane, Rose Wilder
  - Langer, Susanne
  - Laski, Harold J.
  - Lenski. Covey, Lois
  - Lenski, Covey, Lois (Box 262)
  - Lenski, Covey, Lois (Box 263)
  - Lewis, C. Day
  - Lin, Yutang (Box 264)
  - Lin, Yutang, & Walsh, Richard J.
  - Lindsay, Jack
  - Lippincott, Bertram (Box 265)
  - Lobel, Arnold
  - Lofting, Hugh
  - Lofting, Hugh (Box 266)
  - Lofting, Hugh (Box 267)
  - Ludlum, Robert (Box 268)
  - McGinley, Phyllis & Stone
  - McGinley, Phyllis & Stone (Box 269)
  - McMurtry, Larry
  - Marquis, Don
  - Matthews, Brander
  - Maurois, Andre
  - Maurois, Andre (Box 270)
  - Millay, Edna St. Vincent
  - Mitford, Nancy
  - Moorehead, Alan
  - Morris, Richard B.
  - Morris, Wright
  - Murray, Pauli
  - Orwell, George (Box 271)
  - Osborne, John
  - Parker, Sir Gilbert
  - Patchen, Kenneth
  - Pei, Mario A.
  - Priestley, J. B.
  - Rice, Elmer (Box 272)
  - Riefenstahl, Leni
  - Rockwell, Norman
  - Rodgers, Dorothy
  - Rodgers, Mary
  - Roosevelt, Franklin D.
  - Rowse, A. L.
  - Runyon, Damon
  - Runyon, Damon (Box 273)
  - Runyon, Damon (Box 274)
  - Runyon, Damon (Box 275)
  - Salisbury, Harrison
  - Sayers, Dorothy
  - Schoenbrun, David (Box 276)
  - Scott, Hugh D. Jr.
  - Segal, Erich
  - Sinclair, U. B. Jr.
  - Sitwel, Sir Osbert
  - Spark, Muriel
  - Stark, Frega (Box 277)
  - Steele, Welbur Daniel
  - Steinberg, Saul
  - Stolz, Mary
  - Stone, Irvina
  - Sulzberger, C. L.
  - Symons, Julian
  - Taber, Gladys
  - Taber, Gladys (Box 278)
  - Taylor(Burton), Elizabeth
  - Tolstoy, Alexandra
  - Thurber, James
  - Trapp, Maria Augusta
  - Rngerer, Tomi (Jean-Thomas Ungerer)
  - Jpdike, John
  - Uris, Leon
  - Vonnegut, Kurt (Box 279)
  - White, Ethel Lina
  - Wilhelm, Kate
  - Williams, Garth
  - Wright, Richard
  - Zolotow, Charlotte
  - Zolotow, Charlotte & Mary
- Series VII: Booksellers
  - Abraham & Strauss (Box 280)
  - All books
  - Astro-Psychic Awareness Assoc.
  - Amaranth Production Inc.
  - B. Dalton Booksellers
  - Baptist Book Store
  - Baptist Sunday School Board
  - Barr Hust Book Store
  - Ben Franklin Bookstore
  - Bloomingdale's Bros
  - Book Gallery
  - Book Inn
  - Book Store
  - Book World
  - Bookmart
  - Booksmith Dist
  - Borders Book Shop
  - Brentanos
  - Broadway Dept. Store
  - Bullock's
  - Bull's Head Student Store
  - Burrows Brothers Guardian Co.
  - Chandler's
  - Cokesbury
  - Coop
  - Dayton Hudson
  - Des Forges book Store
  - Doubleday
  - Garfinckets (Box 281)
  - J.K. Gill
  - Hatch's Book Store
  - Hathaway House Bookshop
  - Hecht Co.
  - Hickory Stick Bookshops & Whitney Bookshops
  - Higbee Company
  - Hinkle's Book Store
  - Hochschild Kohn
  - J. L. Hudson Co
  - Hunter's Books
  - Intimate Bookshop
  - Ivey's Book Shop
  - Jordan March Company
  - Kaufmann's
  - Book Chat
  - Lazarus
  - Lexington Mall McAlpine's
  - Library Ltd.
  - Macy's
  - Main Street Book Store
  - Marshall Field & Co.
  - May Co.
  - May -- D&F
  - Methodist Publishing House
  - Moderne Book Shop Inc.
  - Nook of Knowledge
  - Paperback Booksmith (Box 282)
  - P.B.S.W.
  - Philobiblon books
  - Pickwick Bookshop
  - Preston Books
  - Rich's Inc.
  - Rike's
  - Robinson's
  - Sanger Harris
  - Scranton's
  - Scribner Book Stores
  - Stewart & Co
  - Tecolote Book Shops
  - University Co-op Society Inc.
  - University Book Store
  - Walden Book Co. Inc.
  - Weinstock's
  - Sam Weller's Zion book Store
  - Westhampton Book Shop
  - Whitney Bookshop & Hickory Stick Bookshop
  - Vassar Cooperative Bookshop
  - Villagara Book Shop
  - Zibart Bros
  - Answered Mail
  - Correspondence Re New Coop Plan, [n.p.], 1966 & 1968 (Box 283)
  - Kroch Brentano
  - Brentano
- Series VIII: Cass Canfield Personal Files
  - C3 (Box 284)
  - Cass Canfield Book Orders, [n.p.], 1971
  - Cass Canfield Book Orders, [n.p.], 1972
  - Canfield, Cass, [n.p.], 1949 -63
    [misc.]
  - Canfield, Cass Century Club Receipts, [n.p.], 1963 -1965
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1961
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1962
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1963
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1964
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1965
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1966 (Box 285)
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1967
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1968
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1969
  - Cass Canfield Donations, [n.p.], 1971
  - Canfield, Mary C. [n.p.], 1949 -1964 (Box 286)
  - Canfield, Mary Cass
  - Canfield, Mary C. Inactive
  - Cass Canfield old passports
  - Farfield Foundation
  - Fishers Island (Box 287)
  - Forman School
  - Freedom House
  - Hammarskjold Memorial Inc. 1966
  - National Arts Center
  - National Foundation, [n.p.], 1956-57
  - National Foundation for Infantile Paralysis
  - New York City Affairs Committee
  - New York Tuberculosis and Health
  - New York University Arts Center October 14th Arts Center Lunch for presenting plan to ladies
  - Pickwick Bookshop
  - Printed: talks, essays, and articles by Cass Canfield
  - River Club of NY
  - State of New York Council on the Arts (Box 288)
  - Szilard, Dr. Leo
  - Theater Inc.
  - United World Federalists, 1951-1956
  - Wartime documents, etc. (Box 289)
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Foundation
  - Woodrow Wilson, [n.p.], 1972
  - Wilson, Woodrow National Fellowship Foundation
  - Woodrow Wilson Fellowship Program (Ford Foundation), [n.p.], 1957 - 1966
- Series IX: Planned Parenthhood and International Planned Parenthood Files
  Consists of bylaws, memos, correspondence
  - PP: Annual banquet, meeting and report (Box 290)
  - "A"
    [Author's file)]
  - Barnett, Robert
  - Best, Winifred
  - Board of Directors
  - Booth-Ferris Foundation
  - Brains Trust
  - Budgets
  - Busby, Horace
  - Bylaws
  - "Ba-Bi" (Box 291)
  - "Bo-Bz"
  - Calderone, Mary S.
  - Campbell, Lorraine
  - Canfield, Jane and Cass
  - Clark, Senator Joseph S.
  - Campton, Randolph
  - Connecticut
  - Congress, U.S.
  - Congress on Population & Environment
  - Copeland, Lammot DuPont
  - "Ca-Cn"
  - "Co-Cz" (Box 292)
  - Draper, William, 1960-1964
  - Draper, William, 1965
  - "D"
  - Executive committee
  - "E" (Box 293)
  - 50th anniversary year
  - Ford Foundation
  - Fund Raising
  - "F"
  - Fund Raising
  - Gruening, Senator Ernest (Box 294)
  - Gunther, John
  - Guttmacher, Dr. Alan
  - "G"
  - Hoeber medical division
  - Huxley, Julian
  - "H"
  - Institute on Man & Science
  - Ittleson, Henry
  - "I"
  - Jaffe, Frederick
  - Joint campaign (Box 295)
  - "J"
  - Kaplan, J. M.
  - Kellogg, Edmund
  - King, Martin Luther, Jr.
  - "K"
  - "L"
  - Lasker, Albert D.
  - Mail campaign
  - Moore, Hugh
  - Mott, Stewart (Box 296)
  - McCormick, Mrs. Stanley
  - "Mc"
  - "M"
  - National directors
  - Nationwide
  - Notre Dame
  - "N" (Box 297)
  - Ogilvy, David
  - Oram, Harold L.
  - "O"
    [Author's file]
  - Pathfinders
  - Pillsbury
  - Population Crisis Committee, [n.p.], 1968-1970 (Box 298)
  - Population Crisis Committee, [n.p.], 1966-1967
  - Population Crisis Committee, [n.p.], 1965
  - Population Institute
  - "P"
  - "Q" (Box 299)
  - Rock, John
  - Rockefeller, John D., III
  - "R"
  - Sanger, Margaret
  - Sheffield, Anne
  - Shockley, Doctor William
  - Statement of Conviction
  - Straus, Donald
  - "Sa-Sm"
  - "Sn-Sz"
  - Tydings, Joseph (Box 300)
  - "T"
  - United Planned Parenthood Campaign
  - "U"
  - Vogt, Doctor William $25,000 fund
  - De Witt, Wallace
  - Washington package
  - Westchester county
  - World population emergency campaign
  - "W"
  - "X-Z"
  - IPPF: A.I.D., [n.p.], 1968 (Box 301)
  - A.I.D., [n.p.], 1964-1967
  - "A"
  - Braestrup, Agnete
  - Bucharest, [n.p.], 1974
  - Budget
  - "B"
  - Cadbury
  - Constitution (Box 302)
  - "C"
  - Day
  - Deverell
  - Draper, William
  - "D"
  - "E"
  - "F"
  - Ford Foundation (Box 303)
  - Fund raising
  - Covering body
  - "G"
  - "H"
  - India
  - "I"
  - "J"
  - Karanuratne
  - "K"
  - "L"
  - Management & planning (Box 304)
  - A.I.D., [n.p.], 1969
  - "M"
  - "N"
  - "O"
  - Pyke, Margaret
  - "P"
  - "Q"
  - Rama Rau (Box 305)
  - Rockefeller, John D., III
  - "R"
  - Santiago Conference
  - Secretary General, [n.p.], 1969
  - Secretary General, [n.p.], 1963-1968
  - Secretary General - Cass Canfield's notes
  - Singapore
  - Stow, Sir John (Box 306)
  - "S"
  - "T"
  - "U"
  - Victor Fund
  - "V"
  - Wallace
  - Western Hemisphere
  - "W"
  - "X, Y, Z"
- Series X: Photographs
  - Abrams, Charles (Box 307)
  - Acheson, Dean
  - Aczel, Tamas
  - Adamic, Louis
  - Adams, Sherman
  - Adams, Charlotte
  - Adenauer
  - Ahlberg, T.J.
  - Albaugh III, William A.
  - Albert, Ramona
  - Albert, Ramona C.
  - Alden, John Richard
  - Aldridge, John
  - Alexander, Tom
  - Rogers, Agnes
  - Allen,TD
  - Alliluyeva,Svetlana
  - Alsop, Joseph
  - Almon, Clopper
  - Alvarez, Walter
  - Amalrik, Andrei
  - Amichai, Yehuda
  - Ammer, Christine
  - Cleveland, Amory
  - Amrine, Michael
  - Anders, Evelyn
  - Anderson, C.W.
  - Wayne, Andrews
  - Ansell, Helen
  - Appleman, Roy E.
  - Argus, M.K.
  - Ariss, Jean
  - Armour, Richard
  - Armstrong, Hamilton Fish
  - Armstrong, William H.
  - Arnold, M.L.
  - Arnold, Edmund C.
  - Ashworth, Bill
  - Astor, Brooke
  - Ata-Ullah, Mohammed
  - Attenborough, David
  - Attwood, William
  - Audemars, Pierre
  - Auerbach, Charlotte
  - Axthelm, Pete
  - Ayme, Marcel
  - Babington, Smith
  - Baccaro, Katherine
  - Bailey, Charles
  - Bald, F. Cleuer
  - Baldwin, Hanson
  - Baldwin, James A. (Box 308)
  - Ball, Harriet
  - Ball, John
  - Ballard, Ernesta
  - Ballinger, Bill S.
  - Balsan, Consuelo Vanderbilt
  - Baukhead, Tallulah
  - Banning, Margaret Culkin
  - Barbash, Jack
  - Barber, Carolyn
  - Bardach, John E.
  - Bardosi, Fulvio
  - Barer, Schlomo
  - Barks, Coleman Byron
  - Barley, Ann
  - Barlow, James
  - Barnes, Djuna
  - Barolini, Antonio
  - Barr, George
  - Barrymore, Ethel
  - Bartlett, Sy
  - Baruch, Dorothy, & Miller, Hyman
  - Barzun, Jacques
  - Barker, William
  - Batchelder, Marjorie
  - Batten, Lindsay
  - Bauer, Erwin
  - Baumbach, Jonathan
  - Bawden, Nina
  - Bayer, Bax
  - Bayles, William D.
  - Beach, Frank
  - Beach, Priscilla
  - Beal, John Robinson
  - Beatty, Charles
  - Becker, Stephen
  - Bee, David
  - Beecher, Marguerite
  - Beldon, Jack
  - Bell, Jack
  - Belote, James
  - Belote, William
  - Bemelmans, Ludwig
  - Bench, Robert E.
  - Benchley, Robert (Box 309)
  - Bendiner, Robert
  - Benedetti, Mario
  - Benedict, Stewart
  - Benoit, Emile
  - Bensman, Joseph
  - Berger, Zdena
  - Berkman, Ted
  - Bertin, Celia
  - Berton, Roueshe
  - Bessie, Simon Michael
  - Beste, R. Vernon
  - Bickel, Alexander M.
  - Biddiss, Michael D.
  - Bingham, Millicent
  - Birmingham, Fred
  - Bishop, JIm
  - Black, Campbell
  - Black, Cyril Edwin
  - Black, Gavin
  - Blaine, Dr. Graham B. JR.
  - Blake, Nicholas
  - Blanc, Suzanne
  - Blaustein, Albert
  - Bliven, Bruce JR.
  - Blossom, Virgil T.
  - Boardman, Neil
  - Boatman, Alan J.
  - Bogdanovich, Peter
  - Bois, J. Samuel
  - Borden, William
  - Bargenicht, Miriam
  - Borkin, Joseph
  - Borneman, Ernest
  - Borsodi, Ralph
  - Bosworth, Allan
  - Boulding, Kenneth
  - Boutwell, William Dow
  - Bowen, M.D. & Angela, J.
  - Bowen, John
  - Bowers, David G. Ph. D.
  - Bowles, Chester
  - Boyce, Richard
  - Boyce, Burke
  - Brackman, Walter
  - Brake, Brian
  - Brean, Herbert
  - Breckinridge, Mary
  - Brede, William J.
  - Breland, Osmond
  - Brenner, Anita
  - Brett, J. Alden
  - Breuer, Bessi
  - Briggs, Peter
  - Briloff, Abraham J.
  - Britton, Beverly
  - Bro, Margueritte Harmon
  - Brodnitz, Dr. Friedrich S.
  - Brogan, D.W. (Box 310)
  - Bromfield, Louis
  - Brooke, James, M.D.
  - Brooks, Gwendolyn
  - Brooks, John Nixon
  - Brooks, Richard
  - Brosnan, Jim
  - Brown, John Mason
  - Browne, Courtney
  - Bruce, Miriam
  - Bruchey, Stewart (Box 311)
  - Bruning, Walter F.
  - Bryan,C.D.B.
  - Brunner, Lousene Rousseau
  - Bryant, Arthur
  - Brzezinski, Zbigniew
  - Buchanan, Russel
  - Buckley, Joseph C.
  - Buckner, Emory
  - Budenz, Louis
  - Burch, Monte
  - Burgess, Adam
  - Burnett, John
  - Burnett, Whit
  - Burns, Gerald
  - Burns, James Mac Gregor
  - Burns, John Horne
  - Burtt, E.A.
  - Busfield, Roger
  - Butterfield, Roger
  - Butz, Otto
  - Byrnes, James
  - Cabot, Blake
  - Caillou, Alan
  - Calahan, Harold Augustin
  - Calder-Marshall, Anthony
  - Calkins, Clinch
  - Cameron, Nigel & Brake, Brian
  - Cameron, Owen
  - Cammarata, Philip
  - Canby, E.
  - Canfield, Mrs Cass
  - Canfield SR, Cass
  - Canfield, Mary Cass
  - Canfield, Michael T.
  - Caples, John
  - Capps, Benjamin
  - Carlsen, Robert
  - Carney, Aubrey
  - Carr, Ante Lee
  - Carr, Albert Z.
  - Carr, John Dickson
  - Carr, Rachel
  - Carrell, Alexis
  - Carrington
  - Carson, Josephine
  - Carson, Rachel
  - Carter, Richard & Stewart Wolf,MD
  - Cary, Joyce (Box 312)
  - Carvic, Heron
  - Caspary, Vera
  - Cassini, Countess
  - Castelot, Andre
  - Catledge, Turner
  - Caulfield, Genevieve
  - Cerf, Bennett
  - Chamberlain, John
  - Chamberlain, Neil W.
  - Chandler, Alfred D.
  - Chandler, Margaret K.
  - Chapin, Katherine Garrison
  - Chapmen, John L.
  - Chapman, F. Spencer
  - Charyn, Jerome
  - Chase, Francis Jr.
  - Chase, Stuart
  - Cheever, John
  - Chekhov, Miclael
  - Childs, Marquis
  - Chotzinoff, Samuel
  - Christiansen
  - Christie, Milton
  - Churchill, Allen
  - Claiborne, Craig
  - Clark, David
  - Clark, Arthur C.
  - Clark, Eugeine
  - Clark, Joseph S.
  - Clark, Kenneth
  - Clark, Kenneth B.
  - Clark, Mark W.
  - Clark, Dr. Thomas D.
  - Clark, Tom
  - Clark, William A.
  - Cleife, Philip
  - Cleveland, Harlan
  - Cleveland, Reginald
  - Clift, Charmian
  - Cobean, Sam
  - Cohane, Tim
  - Cohen, Allan Y.
  - Cohn, Haim (Box 313)
  - Cohn, Norman
  - Colgate Lee
  - Collier, Abram
  - Collingwood, Charles
  - Collins, Clella Reeves
  - Collins, Henry H. JR.
  - Comfort, Alex
  - Comager, Henry Steele
  - Conant, Ralph W.
  - Connell, Brian R.
  - Connolly, Cyril
  - Conrad, Barnaby
  - Cook, Gladys Emerson
  - Cooke & Murray
  - Cobb, John
  - Cooper, Louise
  - Cooper, Morley
  - Cooper, Susan
  - Cores, Lucy
  - Corbett, Lucy
  - Coughlan, Robert
  - Courtney-Brwne, R.
  - Cousteau, Jacques Yves
  - Cowles, Victoria
  - Coyle, Kathleen
  - Craven, W. F.
  - Crisler, Lois
  - Cristol, Vivian
  - Cronin, Vicent
  - Crow, John
  - Cruickshank, Allan
  - Crow, John OP
  - Croy, Homer (Box 314)
  - Cuddan,J.A.
  - Cullen, Countee
  - Cullen, Edward J.
  - Cunti, Merle
  - Cutright, Paul
  - Dale, Virginia
  - Dangerfield, George
  - Daniels, George
  - Darling, Edward
  - Dart, Raymond
  - Davenport, Russell
  - David, Elizabeth
  - Evan, David